const VOCAB = {
  1: [
    // Unit 1-1 Exercise
    {
      question: "사이언스가",
      answer: true,
      choices: [],
    },
    {
      question: "김미나이",
      answer: false,
      choices: [],
    },
    {
      question: "이한성이",
      answer: true,
      choices: [],
    },
    {
      question: "김미나는",
      answer: true,
      choices: [],
    },
    {
      question: "사이언스빌딩는",
      answer: false,
      choices: [],
    },
    {
      question: "이름은",
      answer: true,
      choices: [],
    },
    {
      question: "스타벅스이에요",
      answer: false,
      choices: [],
    },
    {
      question: "수지예요",
      answer: true,
      choices: [],
    },
    {
      question: "이한성이에요",
      answer: true,
      choices: [],
    },
    // Unit 1-2 Exercise
    {
      question: "A: 여기가 조지아텍이에요? \n B: 고마워요.",
      answer: false,
      choices: [],
    },
    {
      question: "A: 이름이 뭐예요? \n B: 아니에요.",
      answer: false,
      choices: [],
    },
    {
      question: "A: 전공이 컴퓨터 사이언스예요. \n B: 저도 바이오메디컬이에요.",
      answer: false,
      choices: [],
    },
    {
      question: "일학년 _____________ .",
      answer: "이에요",
      choices: ["예요", "뭐예요", "이에요"],
    },
    {
      question: "전화번호가 _____________",
      answer: "뭐예요",
      choices: ["예요", "이에요", "뭐예요"],
    },
    {
      question: "이한성",
      answer: "이에요",
      choices: ["이에요", "예요", "뭐예요"],
    },
    {
      question: "김미나",
      answer: "예요",
      choices: ["예요", "이에요", "뭐예요"],
    },
    {
      question: "이름이",
      answer: "뭐예요",
      choices: ["예요", "뭐예요", "이에요"],
    },
  ],

  2: [
    // Unit 2-1 Exercise
    {
      question: "미나 씨는 남자 친구를 있어요?",
      answer: false,
      choices: [],
    },
    {
      question: "어디에 살아요?",
      answer: true,
      choices: [],
    },
    {
      question: "전공이 뭐이에요?",
      answer: false,
      choices: [],
    },
    {
      question: "내일에 만나요.",
      answer: false,
      choices: [],
    },
    // missing a paragraph question
    // Unit 2-2 Exercise
    {
      question: "여기 ____ 뭐 해요?",
      answer: "에서",
      choices: ["에", "에서"],
    },
    {
      question: "조지아텍 ____ 있어요.",
      answer: "에",
      choices: ["에", "에서"],
    },
    {
      question: "기숙사 ____ 책 읽어요.",
      answer: "에서",
      choices: ["에", "에서"],
    },
    {
      question: "테니스 ____",
      answer: "를",
      choices: ["을", "를"],
    },
    {
      question: "책 ____",
      answer: "을",
      choices: ["을", "를"],
    },
    {
      question: "기숙사 ____",
      answer: "를",
      choices: ["을", "를"],
    },
    {
      question: "가다 → 가아요",
      answer: false,
      choices: [],
    },
    {
      question: "하다 → 해요",
      answer: true,
      choices: [],
    },
    {
      question: "보다 → 봐요",
      answer: true,
      choices: [],
    },
    {
      question: "마시다 → 마셔요",
      answer: true,
      choices: [],
    },
    {
      question: "오다 → 오아요",
      answer: false,
      choices: [],
    },
  ],

  3: [
    // Unit 3-1 Exercise
    {
      question: "먹을까요?",
      answer: true,
      choices: [],
    },
    {
      question: "핼까요?",
      answer: false,
      choices: [],
    },
    {
      question: "좋을까요?",
      answer: true,
      choices: [],
    },
    {
      question: "봘까요?",
      answer: false,
      choices: [],
    },
    {
      question: "Choose the correct marker. \n 학교 식당 ____ 좋아요?",
      answer: "이",
      choices: ["를", "이", "가", "을"],
    },
    {
      question: "Choose the correct marker. \n 맛 ____ 없어요.",
      answer: "이",
      choices: ["를", "이", "가", "을"],
    },
    {
      question: "Choose the correct marker. \n 김치 ____ 싫어요?",
      answer: "가",
      choices: ["를", "이", "가", "을"],
    },
    {
      question: "Choose the correct marker. \n 피자 ____ 먹어요.",
      answer: "을",
      choices: ["를", "이", "가", "을"],
    },
    // Unit 3-2 Exercise
    {
      question: "나는 학생이에.",
      answer: false,
      choices: [],
    },
    {
      question: "피자를 먹어.",
      answer: true,
      choices: [],
    },
    {
      question: "공부를 하.",
      answer: false,
      choices: [],
    },
    {
      question:
        "Choose either 아 or 야 when calling someone’s name. \n 한성 ____.",
      answer: "아",
      choices: ["아", "야"],
    },
    {
      question:
        "Choose either 아 or 야 when calling someone’s name. \n 미나 ____.",
      answer: "야",
      choices: ["아", "야"],
    },
    {
      question:
        "Choose either 아 or 야 when calling someone’s name. \n 민수 ____.",
      answer: "야",
      choices: ["아", "야"],
    },
  ],

  4: [
    // Unit 4-1 Exercise
    {
      question: "안 전화할래요?",
      answer: false,
      choices: [],
    },
    {
      question: "커피를 마셜래요?",
      answer: false,
      choices: [],
    },
    {
      question: "테니스를 칠래요?",
      answer: true,
      choices: [],
    },
    {
      question: "공부해고 싶어요.",
      answer: false,
      choices: [],
    },
    {
      question: "TV 봐고 싶어요.",
      answer: false,
      choices: [],
    },
    // Unit 4-2 Exercise
    {
      question: "커피를 마시러 가자.",
      answer: true,
      choices: [],
    },
    {
      question: "한국 음식이 먹으러 가요.",
      answer: false,
      choices: [],
    },
    {
      question: "전공이 컴퓨터 사이언스야?",
      answer: true,
      choices: [],
    },
    {
      question: "피자이라도 살까요?",
      answer: false,
      choices: [],
    },
    {
      question: "제가 팬이야.",
      answer: false,
      choices: [],
    },
  ],

  5: [
    // Unit 5-1 Exercise
    {
      question: "여기 ____ 뭐 해요? ",
      answer: "에서",
      choices: ["에", "에서"],
    },
    {
      question: "조지아텍 ____ 있어요.",
      answer: "에",
      choices: ["에", "에서"],
    },
    {
      question: "기숙사 ____ 책 읽어요.",
      answer: "에서",
      choices: ["에", "에서"],
    },
    {
      question: "테니스 ____",
      answer: "를",
      choices: ["을", "를"],
    },
    {
      question: "책 ____",
      answer: "을",
      choices: ["을", "를"],
    },
    {
      question: "기숙사 ____",
      answer: "를",
      choices: ["을", "를"],
    },
    {
      question: "가다 → 가아요",
      answer: false,
      choices: [],
    },
    {
      question: "하다 → 해요",
      answer: true,
      choices: [],
    },
    {
      question: "보다 → 봐요",
      answer: true,
      choices: [],
    },
    {
      question: "마시다 → 마셔요",
      answer: true,
      choices: [],
    },
    {
      question: "오다 → 오아요",
      answer: false,
      choices: [],
    },
    // Unit 5-2 Exercise
    {
      question: "사궜지요?",
      answer: false,
      choices: [],
    },
    {
      question: "갔지요?",
      answer: true,
      choices: [],
    },
    {
      question: "유명하지요?",
      answer: true,
      choices: [],
    },
    {
      question: "두 명 친구 ",
      answer: false,
      choices: [],
    },
    {
      question: "Find a proper counter. \n 커피 열 ____",
      answer: "잔",
      choices: ["권", "잔", "개", "마리", "학년"],
    },
    {
      question: "Find a proper counter. \n 책상 여덟 _____",
      answer: "개",
      choices: ["권", "잔", "개", "마리", "학년"],
    },
    {
      question: "Find a proper counter. \n 일 ____",
      answer: "학년",
      choices: ["권", "잔", "개", "마리", "학년"],
    },
    {
      question: "Find a proper counter. \n 책 세 ____",
      answer: "권",
      choices: ["권", "잔", "개", "마리", "학년"],
    },
  ],

  6: [
    // Unit 6-1 Exercise
    {
      question: "친구가 알잖아요.",
      answer: true,
      choices: [],
    },
    {
      question: "책을 읽으잖아요.",
      answer: false,
      choices: [],
    },
    {
      question: "난 주문하잖아요.",
      answer: true,
      choices: [],
    },
    {
      question: "주스가 마시잖아요.",
      answer: false,
      choices: [],
    },
    {
      question: "동생이 고등학생잖아요.",
      answer: false,
      choices: [],
    },
    // Unit 6-2 Exercise
    {
      question: "준영이는",
      answer: true,
      choices: [],
    },
    {
      question: "스티브이가",
      answer: false,
      choices: [],
    },
    {
      question: "램프가 위에 책상 있어요.",
      answer: false,
      choices: [],
    },
    {
      question: "기숙사 옆에 식당이 있어요.",
      answer: true,
      choices: [],
    },
    {
      question: "치즈가 안에 냉장고에 있어요.",
      answer: false,
      choices: [],
    },
    {
      question: "Choose the correct marker \n 피자 _____ 책상 위",
      answer: "가",
      choices: ["이", "가", "을", "를", "에", "에서"],
    },
    {
      question: "Choose the correct marker \n ____ 있어요.",
      answer: "에",
      choices: ["이", "가", "을", "를", "에", "에서"],
    },
    {
      question: "Choose the correct marker \n 친구 ____ 도서관 앞",
      answer: "를",
      choices: ["이", "가", "을", "를", "에", "에서"],
    },
    {
      question: "Choose the correct marker \n ____ 만났어요.",
      answer: "에서",
      choices: ["이", "가", "을", "를", "에", "에서"],
    },
    {
      question: "Choose the correct marker \n 마트 오른쪽 _____ 한국 식당",
      answer: "에",
      choices: ["이", "가", "을", "를", "에", "에서"],
    },
    {
      question: "Choose the correct marker \n ____ 있어요.",
      answer: "이",
      choices: ["이", "가", "을", "를", "에", "에서"],
    },
  ],
};
